Guide to the Robert Creeley Computer Files, 1988-2002
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1. Floppy Disks, Robert Creeley's Computer Files contain a total of fifty-one 3 1/2 in. floppy disks. Of these thirty-nine floppy disks have so far been preserved and described in this series.
  - inzip but should be Fax (sent).zip 1/3 Summer '97, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 35)
    Floppy disk contains incoming and outgoing faxes.
    - Faxsent.zip1997 July 15 - 1997 Aug 5 (Folder 1)
  - Faxes Summer 97 #51997, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 36)
    Floppy disk contains faxes.
  - Faxes Summer '97 #41997, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 37)
  - Fax(Received) 3/3 Summer '971997 July 15 - 1997 Oct 31, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 38)
    Floppy disk contains incoming faxes.
    - Faxsent.zip1997 July 15 - 1997 August 6 (Folder 1)
      Received faxes.
    - Msav.rpt1997 Oct 31 (Folder 2)
      Microsoft antivirus report.
  - Fax(Sent).zip 2/3 Summer '971997 July 16 - 1997 Aug 6, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC) (Folder 39)
    - Faxsent.zip1988 July 13 (Folder 1)
      Zipped folder contains outgoing faxes.
  - This zip disk is described in Series 2 as Disk 40., Zip Disk (PC) (Folder 40)
  - Chair 1, 3 1/2" Floppy Disk (PC). Error in File Allocation Table repaired using GetDataBack. (Folder 41)
    Chair correspondence.
    - Restricted Folder. (Folder 1)
      Access to this folder is restricted.
- Series 2. Zip Disks
  Robert Creeley's zip disks are currently unprocessed.
- Series 3. CD-ROMS
  Robert Creeley's CD-ROMS are currently unprocessed.